omniyat.net 2018-06-09

# Privacy Policy

By visiting the Omniyat.net website or any other websites operated by Omniyat.net or its affiliates (collectively, the "Site"), you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Notice, please do not use the Site. Each time you use the Site, you should check the date of this Privacy Notice (which appears above) and review any changes that have been made since your last visit to the Site. As with all shopping websites, we collect personal information from you.

At Omniyat.net, we understand that you value your privacy and wish to have your personal information kept secure, that’s why we are committed to protecting your privacy of any personal information provided to us. Our Privacy Policy describes generally how we manage your personal information and safeguard your right privacy.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES WE COLLECT AND STORE? 

So that we can provide services to you, we may ask for personal details such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. Personal Information is collected when you create an account with us; place an order on the website, or when you communicate to any of our departments such as customer service, sales or technical services through the Site, telephone, email or fax. Some examples of where we may need these details are pre-orders, home deliveries, competitions & promotions and when you opt-in to receiving marketing newsletters from Omniyat.net.

Omniyat.net takes measures to ensure your personal information is protected from unauthorized access, loss, misuse, disclosure or alteration. We also take measures to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information when it is no longer required. The types of measures we take vary with the type of information, and how it is collected and stored.

Generally, you have no obligation to provide any information requested by us. If you choose to withhold requested information however, we may not be able to provide you with the goods and services that depend on the collection of that information.

COLLECTING INFORMATION AND WHAT WE DO WITH IT? 

We respect your privacy. Any personal information that we collect about you will be used and disclosed by us so that we can provide you with the services that you have requested, or otherwise to enable us to carry out our business as suppliers of goods, such as

* Provide our services   
* Respond to your inquiry   
* Customize users' experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates   
* Handle orders, delivery and payments   
* Communicate marketing and promotional offers to you   
* Update our records and maintain any online account you may have with us   
* Enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.   
Each time we use your personal information for advertising purposes such as promotions, surveys and newsletter, we will give you the opportunity to decline to receive any further information from us.

DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

* All information contained by Omniyat.net is treated as strictly confidential and Omniyat.net does not and will not disclose or share such confidential information to / with any external organization.   
* The users’ privacy is very important to us. We do not and shall not at any point in time, either sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties without users’ explicit consent.   
* We may be required from time to time to disclose users’ personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.   
* Omniyat.net also reserves the right to make use of the personal information in any investigation or judicial process relating to fraud on account of such transactions during the period Omniyat.net retains such information.   
* We may also disclose personal information to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protects anyone’s rights, property or safety.   
* We may also share personal information with Corporate affiliates who help detect or prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to).   
* Service providers who help with our business operations.

STORING AND SECURING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the information that you provide us and we will take all reasonable precautions and necessary measures to protect your personal information. Our electronic information systems are password protected to prevent unauthorized access. We have adopted security measures in an effort to protect personal information from loss, misuse or alteration while it is under our control. Our staff are trained and required to protect the privacy of your personal information. In order to maintain this protection, we caution you not to provide your password to anyone. We recommend that, if you share your computer with other people, you close your browser window when your session is completed. Signing off will protect your information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.   
If you believe that your password has been misused, please notify us immediately.

CORRECTING YOUR INFORMATION AND REMOVAL/OPT-OUT

If your name, e-mail, telephone number or other Personal Information changes, you may update, correct or omit the relevant information by going to your profile under “My Account”. If you request us to do so, we will amend any personal information which is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. You may \ directly contact us or send an email at info@omniyat.net. In addition, if you no longer wish to receive communications from us you may opt-out by emailing us at info@omniyat.net or by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any marketing e-mail you receive from us.

CHILDREN AND PRIVACY

The Site is a general audience website and is not directed to children under the age of 13. We will never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has submitted Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files. We understand that children may not fully understand all of the provisions of this Privacy Notice or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Site. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the websites they visit. Omniyat.net does not sell products to persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you are required seek the consent of your parent or guardian to purchase products from the Site.

PAYMENT POLICY

* All credit/debit cards details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties.   
* The Website Policies and Terms & Conditions may be changed or updated occasionally to meet the requirements and standards. Therefore the Customers’ are encouraged to frequently visit these sections in order to be updated about the changes on the website. Modifications will be effective on the day they are posted.   
* Some of the advertisements you see on the Site are selected and delivered by third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers. These third parties may collect information about you and your online activities, either on the Site or on other websites, through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies in an effort to understand your interests and deliver to you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. Please remember that we do not have access to, or control over, the information these third parties may collect. The information practices of these third parties are not covered by this privacy policy.

THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS AND EXTERNAL LINKS 

We maintain relationships with third party affiliates, thus we may feature links to other websites. Although we do not and cannot control the activities of the third parties that operate such websites, you can be sure that we will stop doing business with any affiliate that engages in abusive practices, including, for example, spam, trademark infringement, or unlawful activities. Omniyat.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any other websites besides its own.

REVISIONS TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY 

From time to time it may be necessary for us to amend our privacy policy, thus we reserve the right to its revision, and we strongly suggest that you visit and review our Privacy Policy periodically to make sure you understand how information you provide will be used. However, you can be confident that any changes will be in accordance with the general Privacy Act and the National Privacy Principles.

LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY 

In no event will omniyat.net or its parent, affiliates, licensees or any party involved in creating, producing or delivering the site or its products or services be liable in any manner whatsoever for any incidental, consequential, indirect, special or punitive damages arising out of your access, use or inability to use the site, or in connection with any failure or performance, error, omission, interruption, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus or line or system failure (including loss of profits, loss of business or data, business interruption, and damages that result from inaccuracy of the information or inconvenience, delay, or loss of the use of the site). the foregoing limitations apply whether the alleged liability is based on contract, tort, negligence, strict liability or any other basis, even if omniyat.net or its affiliates or any other party has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS 

In case you want to get in touch with us, or to provide your feedback, we are always there for you. In fact it is a pleasure to hear from our valued customers. Kindly feel free to contact our customer care team via email: support@omniyat.net.
